Story hasn't a halt The echo's fading fast I try
to break the mold
They told me it would never last
They're shutting down the engine
And now it's quiet on the set
Back to the silence and regret This is the price
for being loud Getting lost back in the crowd
After the laughter
The noise we made was all too real
They're terrified of what they feel
So turn the keyboards up again And
hide the anger and the pain
Now it's quiet on the set
Back to the silence and regret This is the price
for being loud Getting lost back in the crowd
The laughter, the laughter
They want to start us safe and light Just close
your eyes and end the fight Just close your
eyes
Now it's quiet on the side
Back to the silence and regret This is the price
for being loud Getting lost back in the crowd
After the laughter
Just cry